dexigner.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy

At Dexigner we recognize that privacy is important.  
This Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by Dexigner.

## Collected Information

Dexigner offers services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

 **Information You Provide**  
When you submit inclusion requests or subscribe to the Dexigner Newsletter, we ask you for personal information such as your name and email address.

 **Cookies**  
When you visit Dexigner, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Dexigner features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

 **Logs**  
When you use Dexigner services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## Methods of processing

Dexigner processes personal information on its servers in the United States of America.

## Information Sharing

Dexigner does not share your personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Dexigner.

## Google AdSense (Google Inc.)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Application and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).  
Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy](http://google.com/privacy/ads/) \- [Opt Out](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout)

## Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
Google Analytics might use Google's Interest-based advertising, 3rd-party audience data and information from the DoubleClick Cookie to extend analytics with demographics, interests and ads interaction data.  
Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) \- [Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

## Disqus (Disqus)

Disqus is a content commenting service provided by Big Heads Labs Inc.  
Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy](http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/) \- [Opt out](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951)

## Quantcast Measure (Quantcast Corporation)

Quantcast Measure is an analytics service provided by Quantcast Corporation.  
Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy) \- [Opt Out](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out)

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
